igaming.org 2017-09-13

# Privacy Policy

We understand what your privacy means to you and we believe it to be as sacred to us as it is to you. To use our wide range of services we do require our visitors to register and provide a bit of personal data and some information regarding your gaming and promotional preferences. But allow us to explain exactly how we gather, maintain and make use of your information:

**Data collection**

The **www.igaming.org** privacy policy applies to any and all information you submit during registration, via email and any other section of this website. To make use of some services offered in this website, you will be required to be a registered member. The registration process is quite simple and fast and you will supply personal information such as your name, email address, location, age and other contact details. You will also be asked a series of multiple choice questions regarding your playing preferences and promotional preferences. This information is used by **www.igaming.org** to better understand your needs and wants so that we may provide a better and more efficient informational service.

In some sections of our website you will have the option to share content (news, articles, promotions, etc.) with your friends and family. Here we will ask you for their names and email addresses just so we can share our content on your behalf.

In either cases where we ask or collect personal data, users will have a choice to opt-in to our mailers, draws and promotions. We will never send unsolicited material to you or referrals without proper authorization. Opting in and out of our mailers is easily done within your profile page. We also pledge never to sell, distribute or trade in part or as a whole any of the information submitted to us by any of our visitors and members.

**Data usage**

**All the information you submit to us will be used to create a personal, private profile for your use only. We will never allow access to this information, sell, share or trade this information unless it has been deemed necessary and obligatory by a court of law.**

**Whenever applicable and only if you have opted in for it, will you receive mailers or other communications from us with promotions and marketing material or other important information concerning your account. Other types of information collected and stored in your computer may include session data such as cookies and is meant to identify you as a registered user, in the case that you may wish to remain logged in to  ** **www.igaming.org** ******or for your system to remember your username and/or other information. These bits of session data will never compromise your privacy or security as they include no personal or contact information. The data in these cookies are also stored in a secure manner and can not be read by third parties.**

****Our commitment****

**We will always strive to provide the most secure and safe system environments and protocols to prevent, deter and avoid any potential or real threats and/or unauthorized parties from reaching and compromising the data we collect.**

****Minor's privacy****

**Anyone under the age of 18 or under the legal age in their respective jurisdictions will not be allowed to register an account with  ** **www.igaming.org** **or any of its sister companies and websites. Anyone wishing to register an account may do so successfully only after ticking the age declaration and Terms & Conditions agreement boxes verifying that they are indeed of legal age and that they agree with our Terms & Conditions.**

**For more information, check the “About us” section or get in touch with us via our “Contact us” section or by e-mailing us at ******[ info@igaming.org](mailto:info@igaming.org)
